<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>skibidi rizz notes</title>
      <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on skibidi rizz notes</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>MCR3U5 - Unit 6</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/MCR3U5---Unit-6</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/MCR3U5---Unit-6</guid>
    <description>L1: Periodic Functions Notes What is a periodic function? A periodic function is a function in which the values of y repeat at regular intervals of θ.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Untitled</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/Untitled</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/Untitled</guid>
    <description> Info ‎ Answer 1 2 3 Info ‎ Answer 1 2 3 hello y .</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>🔢 Dummy Maths Note</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/%F0%9F%94%A2-Dummy-Maths-Note</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/%F0%9F%94%A2-Dummy-Maths-Note</guid>
    <description> Info Switch between light and dark mode to see the difference. Switch between reading and preview mode to see the difference. I am using quick latex plugin for quickly wiriting the formulaes.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Welcome To Out Notes Vault</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</guid>
    <description>Get stated by heading to out Philosophy Or check out the Courses we are currently taking: Functions English.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quote 1</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-1</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-1</guid>
    <description>Macbeth Act 1 Quotes Review This is a review to help you for future quotations tests. For EACH of the following quotations from Macbeth, please answer the following: the speaker (1 mark) the context (where does the phrase occur in the plot/action?) (1 mark) the meaning (paraphrase the quote—put it into your own words) (1 mark) the significance of the quote (explain its importance through character, theme, or descriptive language (2 marks) Further questions to reflect and answers for question 4: How is the quote significant or important in terms of plot? Foreshadowing? What does this quote tell us about the character of the speaker? How does this quotation relate to a theme(s) of the play? (see Theme sheet) How does the descriptive language help us to understand what the character is saying? ACT 1 “That, trusted home,/Might yet enkindle you unto the crown,/Besides the thane of Cawdor.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quote 2-3</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-2-3</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-2-3</guid>
    <description>Macbeth Act 2 and 3 Quotes Review This is a review to help you for future quotations tests. For EACH of the following quotations from Macbeth, please answer the following: the speaker (1 mark) the context (where does the phrase occur in the plot/action?) (1 mark) the meaning (paraphrase the quote—put it into your own words) (1 mark) the significance of the quote (explain its importance through character, theme, or descriptive language) (2 marks) Further questions to reflect and answers for question 4: How is the quote significant or important in terms of plot? Foreshadowing? What does this quote tell us about the character of the speaker? How does this quotation relate to a theme(s) of the play? (see Theme sheet) How does the descriptive language help us to understand what the character is saying? Act 2 “Is this a dagger, which I see before me,/ The handle toward my hand? Come, let me clutch thee.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Question</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Le-Bourgeois-gentilhomme/Question</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Le-Bourgeois-gentilhomme/Question</guid>
    <description>ACTE I, Scène 1 Comment le caractère de M. Jourdain se révèle-t-il progressivement? (p. 25) Les deux maitre commence de parler de l’homme puis les quialité (Stupid) puis dit sont nom.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Notes - Aiden, Aiden, Kristian</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Premiere-Guerre-De-Toronto/Notes---Aiden,-Aiden,-Kristian</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Premiere-Guerre-De-Toronto/Notes---Aiden,-Aiden,-Kristian</guid>
    <description>...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Notes - Ryan</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Premiere-Guerre-De-Toronto/Notes---Ryan</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/French/FIF2D5/Premiere-Guerre-De-Toronto/Notes---Ryan</guid>
    <description>Part 1 - Choisir sa voie Chapter 1 Napoleon Chapter starts with a count from referee Alfonso Bunnelli, is an Italian boxer Bunnelli punches hard and fast Fred Belanger is his coach His ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Philosophy</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/About/Philosophy</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/About/Philosophy</guid>
    <description>This vault is designed to be as bare bones as possible, and to look as good as possible in default obsidian (dark mode)… However: A theme is recommended for the best/most aesthetic experience ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>