<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>skibidi rizz notes</title>
      <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on skibidi rizz notes</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>MCR3U5 - Unit 6</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/MCR3U5---Unit-6</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/MCR3U5---Unit-6</guid>
    <description>L1: Periodic Functions Notes What is a periodic function? A periodic function is a function in which the values of y repeat at regular intervals of θ.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>🔢 Dummy Maths Note</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/%F0%9F%94%A2-Dummy-Maths-Note</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/Math/MCR3U5/%F0%9F%94%A2-Dummy-Maths-Note</guid>
    <description> Info Switch between light and dark mode to see the difference. Switch between reading and preview mode to see the difference. I am using quick latex plugin for quickly wiriting the formulaes.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/</guid>
    <description>Needed as a front page so website does not shit itself.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Philosophy</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/About/Philosophy</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/About/Philosophy</guid>
    <description>This vault is designed to be as bare bones as possible, and to look as good as possible in default obsidian (dark mode)… However: A theme is recommended for the best/most aesthetic experience ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quotes - Act 1-2</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Macbeth/Quotes---Act-1-2</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Macbeth/Quotes---Act-1-2</guid>
    <description>Macbeth quotes act 1 Act 1, Scene 1 ”Fair is foul, and foul is fair. Hover through the fog and filthy air” The speakers are the witches, together, not speaking to anyone else It is said in the opening of the play, after they’ve decided to see Macbeth after the battle is over They are saying that fair or good, will now be foul or bad it uses the literary device of a paradox helps establish the theme of good vs evil Act 1, Scene 3 ”Not so happy, yet much happier” The witches say this to Banquo It is said when the witches first meet with Macbeth and Banquo They are saying that Banquo will not be as happy/fortunate as Macbeth, but also very happy/fortunate at the same time.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quotes Test Info</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Macbeth/Quotes-Test-Info</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Macbeth/Quotes-Test-Info</guid>
    <description>Macbeth quotes test important information For Macbeth, there will be many quotes you need to know they will probably have some implication on plot or theme, or characterization, ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Short Story Review - Messina</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Unit-1---Short-Stories/Short-Story-Review---Messina</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Unit-1---Short-Stories/Short-Story-Review---Messina</guid>
    <description>Short Story Review Be able to define &amp; identify Characterization | Direct vs Indirect | Static vs Dynamic | The process by which the writer reveals the personality of a character ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Study Sheet</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Unit-1---Short-Stories/Study-Sheet</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1---Ryan-H/Unit-1---Short-Stories/Study-Sheet</guid>
    <description>Short Story Unit Study Sheet A short story: Focuses on a single incident One setting Focuses on a limited number of characters (generally 1 or 2) Setting Time and place of the story, ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quote 1</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-1</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-1</guid>
    <description>Macbeth Act 1 Quotes Review This is a review to help you for future quotations tests. For EACH of the following quotations from Macbeth, please answer the following: the speaker (1 mark) the context (where does the phrase occur in the plot/action?) (1 mark) the meaning (paraphrase the quote—put it into your own words) (1 mark) the significance of the quote (explain its importance through character, theme, or descriptive language (2 marks) Further questions to reflect and answers for question 4: How is the quote significant or important in terms of plot? Foreshadowing? What does this quote tell us about the character of the speaker? How does this quotation relate to a theme(s) of the play? (see Theme sheet) How does the descriptive language help us to understand what the character is saying? ACT 1 “That, trusted home,/Might yet enkindle you unto the crown,/Besides the thane of Cawdor.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quote 2-3</title>
    <link>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-2-3</link>
    <guid>https://notes-and-shit.github.io/English/ENG2D1/Quote-2-3</guid>
    <description>Macbeth Act 2 and 3 Quotes Review This is a review to help you for future quotations tests. For EACH of the following quotations from Macbeth, please answer the following: the speaker (1 mark) the context (where does the phrase occur in the plot/action?) (1 mark) the meaning (paraphrase the quote—put it into your own words) (1 mark) the significance of the quote (explain its importance through character, theme, or descriptive language) (2 marks) Further questions to reflect and answers for question 4: How is the quote significant or important in terms of plot? Foreshadowing? What does this quote tell us about the character of the speaker? How does this quotation relate to a theme(s) of the play? (see Theme sheet) How does the descriptive language help us to understand what the character is saying? Act 2 “Is this a dagger, which I see before me,/ The handle toward my hand? Come, let me clutch thee.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>